Did that get you?
I kissed Yukiya for the first time.
We kissed.
I suck.
Why am I so not cute?
Ohagi
I'm... gone.
M-M-Miku!
Are you okay? Are you alive?
Should I call an ambulance?
I should! I'm doing it!
Wait, wait.
What's wrong? What's going on?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I just have a bit of a fever.
I'll be back at school tomorrow.
Oh, thank goodness, what a relief.
Asagi-kun?!
What does she mean, she's okay?
Her voice...
That's her voice after
she's been crying!
I...
I made her cry!
Why does my body react so easily?
Asagi-kun was so worried
about you that he talked to me!
I skipped school
right after what happened.
Of course he's worried.
But I don't know how
I should act on the phone.
I'm making Yukiya worry again.
I'm such a piece of crap.
m 637.89 471.15 l 940.14 384 915.3 316.14 1052.7 274.77 1077.51 342.63 1324.98 268.14 1372.98 393.09 662.91 604.98 650.49 539.58 625.65 483.3
I'm at your door. Can you come out?
Now
Don't put on such a needy face.
Buck up!
What's up?
What about school?
I thought you might need some stuff.
Flu Medicine
Can I come in?
Yeah.
I Want to End This Love Game
Is your fever bad?
Episode 11
My Childhood Friend Embraces Me
Yeah.
It's okay right now, though.
You're pretty hot.
I-I'm all sweaty right now.
And nasty.
I don't care at all.
Sorry for waking you.
Don't you have ice pillows or anything?
I think in the fridge, maybe.
You do?
Why aren't you using it?
Where's Auntie today?
She seems to be busy at
the hospital these days.
She's been there since last night.
Yeah?
Thanks.
And here.
Stay hydrated.
And medicine.
I didn't know if you had any at
home, so I bought a few kinds.
Did you eat?
Can you?
Yeah.
I don't want to bother you, though.
You're so crabby.
I grant you the title of
"Crabbiest Person in Town."
That's you.
You're going to need something
to wipe down with before you eat.
Miku
Wakana
Our guest has reported on
the hottest new home appliances.
TOP 3 MOST POPULAR HOME APPLIANCES
1st Place: Robot Vacuum
2nd Place: Automatic Cooker
In our next segment,
we'll show you some training exercises
to build up your stamina.
Pardon me.
You can finish up yourself, yeah?
S-Sure, sure.
Were you secretly anticipating me
wiping you down?
I wasn't!
Well, I'm going to make some food.
Be a good girl and get
changed in the meantime.
Thanks for the meal.
Sorry it's just a microwave dinner.
I could have made her something
more nutritious if I could cook.
It's good, though,
because you prepared it.
Oh, hey...
Do you have anything
leftover from dinner or anything?
Huh? No. Why?
It's just that I forgot
to buy lunch for myself today.
He rushed over in such a hurry?
You're so stupid.
You bought so much stuff.
I can't finish all of that myself.
You can have some.
No, that's yours.
Why are you being so
stubborn about that?
Yukiya's so nice.
Yukiya's so nice, and yet
I caused him so much trouble
by doing dumb shit.
I have to apologize.
That's what a cute girl would do.
Hey...
About the Pokitto game...
I Want to End This Love Game
I'm sorry about everything.
No, it's totally fine.
I was...
Well...
I have to tell him.
Properly.
That kiss didn't count.
I got jealous and used a kiss
to try to win the game.
I never knew you were the type
to kiss for that sort of reason.
I can't blame him
if he gets sick of me.
I used a dirty trick
to try to get his attention.
I deserve this.
I, uh...
You were pissed about me
installing Instantgram, weren't you?
So you did that
in the heat of the moment.
W-Well, yeah, that's true, but...
Look.
Posts                         Followers                    Following
Edit Profile
I have no intention of following
anyone other than you.
I was going to use it just
as an album for the two of us.
Did that take your breath away?
Maybe he's telling me
I don't have to say anything.
I...
don't deserve any more
kindness from you.
I'm so underhanded.
I'm the worst kind of girl.
Well, sure, you have your issues.
You get really nasty
when you're gaming.
Tap, tap, tap, tap
Miku in Yukiya's mind
Are you bored of the Love Game?
And you're a whiner.
And you boss me around.
You get annoyingly stubborn about
certain things, like right now.
And you're way more complicated
now than you used to be.
But I don't hate that about you.
I envy how you can be
so committed to things.
I admire how you can speak your mind.
You used to be a crybaby, and now
you're strong enough to talk back to me.
All the things I'd get
fed up with and abandon,
you keep at them no matter what.
Even including all the parts
you could do better on, I lo—
look up to.
So don't...
Anyway, point is...
This is the point.
What is your point?
Don't get the wrong idea.
It's just that I stand a better chance
if you have some flaws... in the game.
Well, y'know, I'm used to dealing with
high-maintenance girls thanks to Wakana.
Not that there's many people
who can look after you.
Besides, think about how I feel,
being compared to you
because we've known each other
since we were kids.
Try being a little less perfect.
Say what?
Miku...
Thanks.
Yeah, you look the best
when you're smiling.
I-Imma post a picture of you
weak from your fever.
Wha?!
Stop it! Delete it!
You're rarely like this.
I'm never deleting it.
Added to the Mikudex.
I'm not a Puchimon!
Natsuki
Incoming Call
N-Nacchan.
What's up?
Miku!
We're on lunch break right now.
Asagi-kun hasn't come back
since he darted out of school.
Oh, yeah.
Actually, he's at my place right now.
I knew it!
Natsuki
Call Connected
Guys! Asagi-kun's at Miku's place!
I knew it!
Lucky!
Green Tea
Oh, to be young!
Nacchan!
Why did you tell them?!
S-Sorry!
Ooh, Asagi-kun!
I can't go to school anymore!
I'm skipping school tomorrow!
I can't either! No school!
You idiot, it'll be even worse
if we both skip school!
You go!
You aren't even sick! You go!
You said you'd be fine by tomorrow!
My fever got worse thanks to you!
All right, you need to get
some sleep for tomorrow.
'kay, good night.
Hey! You shoved me!
I'm sick, you know!
Ow!
Great, you dislocated my shoulder.
Time to stay home.
Yeah.
I love Yukiya.
So much.
Weird...
What is this?
It isn't the same feeling as yesterday.
It's the same, but I can tell this time.
I don't know,
but I don't hate how I feel.
I want to kiss Yukiya.
Is your fever getting worse?
Your face is red and
your eyes are watery.
I'll stick around for a while longer.
Get some sleep.
What is this?
I feel so anxious.
Something feels different from before.
Next Time
My Childhood Friend Is Girly
The next episode of I Want
to End This Love Game.
Final episode:
"My Childhood Friend Is Girly."
See you there!